gtanet.com 2019-10-15

# GTANet.com - Now With Added Vitamins! : Cookies and Privacy Policy

  |    

At GTANet, we recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. This policy outlines what information may be collected when you visit our web sites or use our apps, how that information is used, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

"The GTA Network", "GTA Network" and "GTANet" are terms used in this policy to refer to all of our web sites and applications. When you continue to visit our web sites, you are consenting to the practices described in this policy.

## Log Files

Like most websites, our web sites collect and use data stored in log files. The information we collect and store includes Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type and versions, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., contained within anonymous statistical log files for are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on our web sites to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

## Google AdSense and DoubleClick DART Cookies and Privacy

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher web sites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google�s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (�interest based targeting�).

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses �non personally identifiable information�. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other web sites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Sovrn / Lijit Cookies and Privacy

One of the ad networks and companies The GTA Network utilizes is Lijit Networks Inc. Lijit's privacy policy can be viewed at [http://www.lijit.com/company/privacy-policy](https://www.lijit.com/company/privacy-policy). Lijit collects only anonymous information unless a reader chooses to submit personal information to Lijit. Lijit permits readers to opt out of the collection of this anonymous site visit data through the Lijit opt-out tool at [http://www.lijit.com/choices](https://www.lijit.com/choices).

## Game Advertising Online ("GAO") Cookies and Privacy

One of the ad networks and companies The GTA Network utilizes is Game Advertising Online. GAO's privacy policy can be viewed at [https://www.game-advertising-online.com/?section=doc&action=privacy](https://www.game-advertising-online.com/?section=doc&action=privacy).

## Links and External Resources

This Web site contains links to other web sites and resources. Please be aware that The GTA Network is not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites and resources. The GTA Network encourages you, when you leave our web sites, to read the privacy policy (or privacy statement) of each and every web site you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to our web sites and applications.

## Contacting The GTA Network Regarding This Policy

If you have any questions about this policy please send a private message to an administrator or moderator via the private messaging facility at [GTAForums.com](https://gtaforums.com/), or post a public message in our GTA Network Support forum at <https://gtaforums.com/forum/2-gta-network-support/>

## Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to update or change this privacy policy at any time. Any such change, modification, or addition to the privacy policy on The GTA Network will become effective immediately upon posting on the site.

This policy was last updated on the 22nd of June, 2014.

|  |
